# OJELERE ADELODUN EMMANUEL

Tel: (+234) 706 259 7601, 08050993730

Email: adelodun.emmanuel@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

A polite and motivated professional Customer service individual with over 4 years proven experience in managing relationships between business and customers. Good communication skill, interpersonal skill and problem-solving skills. Committed to maintaining relationships to increase profitability and drive business results.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth:

21st December, 1987

Sex:

Male

Marital status:

Married

State of origin:

Oyo state

Languages known:

**English and Yoruba** 

# **CORE COMPETENCES**

• CRM 365

• Avaya (Email and Call)

Microsoft office

 Hootsuite (Social Media – Facebook, Instagram and Twitter)

• Microsoft Teams

Finacle

#### WORK HISTORY

2018 - Current

FirstBank of Nigeria, Limited

Client Service Group (Provider HR Indexx Ltd)

# FirstContact Voice Inbound July 2018 to Aug 2019

- Achieved high satisfaction rating through proactive one-call resolutions of customer issues.
- Handle complaints, enquiries and request via the telephone

### Digital Interaction (Email Administration) Sept 2019 to May 2021

- Handle enquiries, complaints and requests coming in through the FirstContact mailbox.
- Generate daily email interaction reports for collation and paste individual email register on the unit's continuous email register

# Digital Interaction (Social Media Specialist) June 2021 till date

- Handle complaints coming in through the Social Media platform (Facebook, Instagram, & Twitter)
- Assisting other consultants from Voice Inbound and email Admin (Assistance TeamLead)

2017-2018

**National Youth Service Corps (A003691721)** 

NYSC Nursery & Primary School Tambuwal Sokoto State (PPA)

# **Unified Payment Services, Ltd (Provider: Integrated Corporate Services Ltd)**

### **Service Executive**

- Captured customer feedback to communicate to superiors for ongoing improvement.
- Maintained composure when faced with difficult customer situations
- Interpreted management directives to define and document administrative staff processes.
- Monitored employees and customer interactions to assess quality of service.

### **CERTIFICATION**

- Coursera Certification on Soft skills Course by Jobberman, 2021
- Effective Contact Centre Agent Certification Training by NLP Ltd, 2020
- Graduate Member (GNIM) Nigerian Institute of Management (Chartered) 2018
- Associate Member (ACILRM) Chartered institute of Loan & Risk Management 2018

#### **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2016 **Bachelor of Science: Banking and Finance (Matric Number 2013/2004)** Federal University of Agriculture Abeokuta – Abeokuta Ogun State

2009 – 2011 **Ordinary National Diploma: Insurance (Upper credit)**Lagos State Polytechnic, Isolo Lagos

#### RESEARCH WORKS

The Effect of Liquidity Management on Banks' Profitability in Nigeria 2016 The Impact of Inflation on Life Assurance Business in Nigeria 2011

### **VOLUNTEER AND LEADERSHIP POSITION HELD**

- President, INEC CDS Group Tambuwal Zone Sokoto State, Oct 2017 to April 2018
- Zonal Evang. Secretary Nigeria Christian Corpers' Fellowship, Oct 2017 to April 2018
- General Secretary, National Association of Banking and Finance Students , 2016

### REFERENCES

Available on request